http://www.all-languages.org.uk/terms-and-conditions/

Privacy Statement
The Association for Language Learning is a registered charity in England and Wales (registered charity number 1001826). The ALL office can be contacted at the following address: Association for Language Learning, Voluntary Action LeicesterShire, 9 Newarke Street, Leicester LE1 5SN. Telephone: 0116 478 8200. Email: info@all-languages.org.uk.
This notice explains how and why we collect, hold and use your personal information.
If you no longer wish us to process your personal data you can at any time ask us to stop by emailing us at info@all-languages.org.uk
This privacy notice covers:
Why we use your personal information
The legal basis for processing
What personal information we use
How we use your personal information
Your rights under data protection legislation
Sharing personal information with third parties
How long we may keep your information
Changes to our privacy notice
Contact details for our Data Protection Officer
Why we use your personal information
We process your personal data for the following purposes:
To ensure you receive the service, product or information you have requested or bought from us
Carry out reasonable administration of your membership, bookings, volunteering, donations and other services
Keep in touch with you in the way that you wish us to
Better understand our users and members to enable us to improve the services we offer – for example for research and statistical analysis including usage patterns
We only use the data in an anonymized manner when we use your data for this purpose.
to enable us to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations
to offer new products and services to you which are relevant and appropriate, and only to the extent that would be reasonably expected.
If we plan to introduce further processes for the use of your information, we will provide information about that purpose prior to such processing.
The legal basis for processing
Under Data Protection Law, there are various grounds which are considered to be a ‘legal basis for processing’.
The legal basis for processing should be determined by the Data Controller.
Where we are the Data Processor, the legal basis is determined by the Customer. Typically, the legal basis in this scenario is:
‘processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest’
Where we are the Data Controller, the legal basis for processing is based on:
‘processing is necessary for the purposes of legitimate interests pursued by the controller’
It should be noted that in some circumstances this legal basis may vary, however, we always operate in full compliance with Data Protection Law and will only process data with a fair and reasonable legal basis for doing so.
What personal information we process
In order to carry out these services, we obtain and process the following chart:
Data Subject (Who)
Data Category (What)
Description of data obtained
Individual Member
Forename
This is the forename of the member
Individual Member
Surname
This is the surname of the member
Individual Member
Salutation
This is the member’s salutation.
Individual Member
Job Title
This is the members job title at time of record
Individual Member
Place of work
This is the members place of work at time of record
Individual Member
Payment method
This is the method of payment for membership
Individual Member
Payment History and balances
This is the member’s history of payment transactions, including subscriptions, refunds and balances
Individual Member
Payment card details
Payment card details are captured and passed to a 3rd party for authorisation.
Individual Member
Postal Address
The member’s postal address
Individual Member
Identifiers
This is the membership number used to identify a members record
Individual Member
Authentication data
Username and password, single-sign-or multi-factor-authentication tokens
Individual Member
Email Address
This is the primary contact telephone number of the member
Individual Member
Telephone number
This is the primary contact email address of the member used to receive communications from ALL
Representative of member organisation
Forename
This is the forename of the representative of member organisation
Representative of member organisation
Surname
This is the surname of the representative of member organisation
Representative of member organisation
Gender
This is the member’s gender
Representative of member organisation
Membership type
This is the grade of membership
Representative of member organisation
Salutation
This is the representative of member organisation salutation.
Representative of member organisation
Job Title
This is the job title of the representative of member organisation at time of record
Representative of member organisation
Place of work
This is the members place of work at time of record
Representative of member organisation
Payment method
This is the method of payment for membership
Representative of member organisation
Payment History and balances
This is the member’s history of payment transactions, including subscriptions, refunds and balances
Representative of member organisation
Payment card details
Payment card details are captured and passed to a 3rd party for authorisation.
Representative of member organisation
Identifiers
This is the membership number used to identify a members record
Representative of member organisation
Authentication data
Username and password, single-sign-or multi-factor-authentication tokens
Representative of member organisation
Postal Address
The organisation’s postal address
Representative of member organisation
Email Address
This is the primary contact telephone number of the representative of member organisation used to receive communications from ALL
Representative of member organisation
Additional Email Address
This is the primary contact telephone number of the representative of member organisation
Representative of member organisation
Telephone number
This is the primary contact email address of the representative of member organisation
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Title
This is the contact’s title (Mr, Mrs, Ms, etc).
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Forename
This is the contact’s forename.
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Surname
This is the contact’s surname.
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Authentication data
Username and password, single-sign-or multi-factor-authentication tokens
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Gender
The contact’s gender (Salutation)
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
House Name
The text entered as the contact’s house name.
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Street
The text entered as the contact’s street.
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Locality
The text entered as the contact’s locality.
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Town
The text entered as the contact’s town.
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Postcode
The text entered as the contact’s post code.
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Mobile Telephone
This is the contact’s mobile telephone number used to receive information on membership
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Email
This is the contact’s E-mail address used to receive communications from ALL, including purchase confirmations and purchase downloads
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Payment History and balances
This is the member’s history of payment transactions, including  purchases and refunds
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Payment card details
Payment card details are captured and passed to a 3rd party for authorisation.
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Shop information
ALL website can be used as a payment page from externally or internally hosted shop systems. This the information captured as part of that (“shopping basket”).
Contact (lapsed member, shop)
Browser Details
IP address, cookies, browser information
Website Access
IP Address
The network address of your device or internet connection
Website Access
Browser Type and Version
The type of Web Browser your device is using
Website Access
Cookies
Special records in your browser to help the website operate
Website Access
Web Analytics
Generalised information about browsing behaviour and page statistics
How we process your personal information
We use your personal information, and some of our employees have access to such information, only to the extent required to carry out the services for you.
We have introduced appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of your personal information during storage, processing and transit.
ALL only processes your personal information in the UK.
Your rights under Data Protection Law
Right to Access
You have the right of access to your personal information that we process and details about that processing.
If you are a current member of ALL you can usually access that information directly from our website. However, should this not be possible, you can raise a Data Subject Access Request (DSAR) to receive this information in another format.
Right to Rectification
You have the right to request that information is corrected if it’s inaccurate.  If you are a current member of ALL you can usually update your own information directly in our website.  However, should this not be possible, you can contact us to make the changes on your behalf.
Right to Erasure (Right to be Forgotten)
You have the right to request that your information is removed; depending on the circumstances, we may or may not be obliged to action this request.
Right to Object
You have the right to object to the processing of your information; depending on the circumstances, we may or may not be obliged to action this request.
Right to Restriction of Processing
You have the right to request that we restrict the extent of our processing activities; depending on the circumstances, we may or may not be obliged to action this request.
Right to Data Portability
You have the right to receive the personal data which you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format suitable for transferring to another controller.
Right to lodge a complaint
If you think we have infringed your privacy rights, you can lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority. You can lodge your complaint in particular in the country where your live, your place of work or place whereby you believe we infringed your right(s).
You can exercise your rights be sending an e-mail to info@all-languages.org.uk  Please state clearly in the subject that your request concerns a privacy matter, and provide a clear description of your requirements.
Sharing personal information with third parties
We use a range of trusted service providers to help deliver our services. All of our suppliers are subject to appropriate safeguards, operating in accordance with our specific instructions and limitations, and in full compliance with Data Protection Law.
These service providers include:
Payment Processors – to securely process your card payments (we do not see, or store payment card details)
Email Providers – to send out our email notifications or messages to ALL members, current and lapsed
Hosting Providers – to manage our secure enterprise data centres
Security Providers – to protect our systems from attack
Telephony Providers – we might record calls for training, quality and security purposes
Mailing houses – we provide postal and member data to enable the mailing of printed materials (e.g. Languages Today)
We may also have access to your personal information as part of delivering the service. If we need to change or add additional third parties, we will always update our Privacy Notice accordingly. We will only disclose your information to other parties in the following limited circumstances
where we are legally obliged to do so, e.g. to law enforcement and regulatory authorities
where there is a duty to disclose in the public interest
where disclosure is necessary to protect our interest e.g. to prevent or detect crime and fraud
where you give us permission to do so e.g. by providing consent within our website or via an online application or consent form
How long will we keep your personal information
We will only retain information for as long as is necessary to deliver the service safely and securely. We may need to retain some records to maintain compliance with other applicable legislation – for example finance, taxation, fraud and money laundering law requires certain records to be retained for an extended duration, in some cases for up to seven years.
Changes to our Privacy Notice
This policy will be reviewed regularly and updated versions will be posted on our websites.
Contact details for our Data Protection Officer
We have appointed a Data Protection Officer (DPO); their contact details are as follows:
Rachel Middleton, Director of ALL
Association for Language Learning,
Voluntary Action LeicesterShire,
9 Newarke Street,
Leicester LE1 5SN.
Telephone: 0116 478 8200
Email: rachelm@all-languages.org.uk
What to do if you’re not happy
In the first instance, please talk to us directly so we can resolve any problem or query.
You also have the right to contact the Information Commissions Office (ICO) if you have any questions about Data Protection, or if you would like to make a complaint. You can contact them using their help line 0303 123 113 or at www.ico.org.uk.
For broader advice and guidance please contact the data protection regulator:
The Information Commissioner
Wycliffe House
Water Lane
Wilmslow
Cheshire SK9 5AF
Telephone: 01625-545700
Fax: 01625 524510
Terms and Conditions - Individual, Student/NQT and Group Membership
1. Consumer Contracts Regulations (2014)
The Association for Language Learning is a registered charity in England and Wales (registered charity number 1001826). The ALL office can be contacted at the following address: Association for Language Learning, Voluntary Action LeicesterShire, 9 Newarke Street, Leicester LE1 5SN. Telephone: 0116 478 8200. Email: info@all-languages.org.uk.
Through purchasing an individual membership subscription you gain personal access to the benefits of belonging to ALL. Through purchasing a group membership subscription, all languages teaching staff of a single institution gain access to the benefits of belonging to ALL.
Group membership applies to a single institution only. If your school is part of an Academy Trust, the group membership will apply to languages teaching staff of your school only and shall not include any other schools within the Academy Trust. Group membership does not allow any member of the group voting rights or election to committees or office.
ALL member benefits and the means of accessing them are outlined on the membership information pages of the ALL website.
The cost and the different membership packages available are shown on the membership information pages of the ALL website. Membership subscriptions for ALL are not subject to VAT.
You can contact the ALL office using the details above if you need help with understanding the membership information provided on the ALL website.
The total cost of your membership subscription is shown on the checkout page of the online joining form. Membership must be paid in full within 45 days of the due date. Instalments are not offered. For new members, the due date is the date you submitted your membership application. For renewing members, the due date is your renewal date.
ALL accepts payment via online card payment, BACS, cheque, and card payment over the phone. Individual members can also opt to set up a Direct Debit. If you do not make an online card payment at the time of joining online, you will be sent an invoice via email detailing the payment methods available to you. You can contact the ALL office using the details above to request more information on the membership balance outstanding and about the methods of payment available.
1.1 Cancellation policy for new members
You have the right to cancel your ALL membership and receive a refund within 14 days of making your membership application, provided you do not access the exclusive online resources available in the online ALL Members' Area.
If you access the exclusive online resources available in the online ALL Members'Area before the expiry of the 14 day period, you are deemed to have waived your cancellation rights under the terms of the Consumer Contracts Regulations 2014 and you will not be permitted to receive a refund.
If you join online, the date of your membership application is the date you completed the online form. If you join by an offline method such as a phone call or paper membership form, the date of your application is the day the phone call or the paper form is received by the ALL office.
Beyond the 14 day period, you can cancel your ALL membership at any time. No refund will be given.
To cancel your ALL membership, you must submit a request to ALL in writing by post or by email to info@all-languages.org.uk.
1.2 Membership renewal
Your ALL membership works on the premise of continuous membership. A new subscription will automatically be created for you at your renewal date. You will be sent email reminders to make payment for your new subscription in advance of the renewal date
ALL membership lasts for one calendar year from the date your membership application is received. If your membership application is received between the 1st to the 14th of the month (inclusive), your renewal date will be set to the 1st of that month, one calendar year later. If your membership application is received on the 15th or later of the month, your renewal date will be set to the 1st of the next month, one calendar year later. Your renewal date is displayed on your membership card and within the self service pages of the online ALL Members Area. You can also contact the ALL office using the information shown above for information on when your renewal is due.
1.3 Cancellation policy for renewing members
If you have received a renewal reminder and do not wish to continue your ALL membership, you must inform ALL in writing by post or by email to info@all-languages.org.uk no more than 45 days after your membership renewal date.
If your membership renewal fee remains unpaid after 45 days, your membership will be lapsed and you will no longer have access to the ALL membership benefits.
2. Data Protection
The terms of ALL's data protection notification can be viewed on the Information Commissioner's website. (https://ico.org.uk/).
Any personal information you provide as part of your ALL membership application will be processed in accordance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998.
2.1 How will my information be used?
ALL collects, stores and processes your information in order to administer your ALL membership and deliver your membership benefits. The information is also used to support ALL marketing, sales, fundraising, events and research activities. Data will be retained by ALL if the membership is lapsed.
2.2 How do I make a choice about how my information is used?
You have a choice about whether you want to receive information about ALL and other organisations' activities and opportunities, and by which channels. We will not use your personal information for these purposes if you have indicated that you do not wish us to do so. You can change your preferences at any time by contacting the ALL office:
Association for Language Learning
Voluntary Action LeicesterShire
9 Newarke Street
Leicester
LE1 5SN
Email: info@all-languages.org.uk
Association for Language Learning is a registered charity in England and Wales. Its registration number is 1001826.
Terms and Conditions - Corporate Membership
1. Consumer Contracts Regulations (2014)
The Association for Language Learning is a registered charity in England and Wales (registered charity number 1001826). The ALL office can be contacted at the following address: Association for Language Learning,Voluntary Action Leicestershire, 9 Newarke Street
Leicester, LE1 5SN. Telephone: 0116 478 8200. Email: info@all-languages.org.uk
Through purchasing a corporate membership subscription, a single organisation or company gains access to the benefits of ALL Corporate Membership. We recommend the main contact be part of your organisation’s marketing and sales team.
Corporate membership does not allow any employee or associate of the organisation ALL voting rights or election to ALL committees or office.
ALL member benefits and the means of accessing them are outlined on the membership information pages of the ALL website.
The cost and the different membership packages available are shown on the membership information pages of the ALL website. Membership subscriptions for ALL are not subject to VAT.
You can contact the ALL office using the details above if you need help with understanding the membership information provided on the ALL website.
The total cost of your membership subscription is shown on the checkout page of the online joining form. Membership must be paid in full within 45 days of the due date. Instalments are not offered. For new members, the due date is the date you submitted your membership application. For renewing members, the due date is your renewal date.
ALL accepts payment via online card payment, BACS, cheque, and card payment over the phone. No Direct Debit options are open to corporate members. If you do not make an online card payment at the time of joining online, you will be sent an invoice via email detailing the payment methods available to you. You can contact the ALL office using the details above to request more information on the membership balance outstanding and about the methods of payment available.
1.1 Cancellation policy for new Corporate members
You have the right to cancel your ALL membership and receive a refund within 14 days of making your membership application, provided you have not accessed the exclusive benefits of ALL Corporate Membership, which include, but are not restricted to:
- placing a discounted advertising booking through any of ALL’s online or offline channels;
- your news, events and special offers being featured in any of ALL’s online or offline channels, for example the “Corporate Member News” area of the ALL website or the ALLNet e-bulletin;
- tweeting or posting your promotions to the ALL social media accounts;
- fostering relationships with ALL local groups;
- accessing the exclusive online resources available in the online ALL Members’ Area.
If you access any of the ALL Corporate Member benefits before the expiry of the 14 day period, you are deemed to have waived your cancellation rights under the terms of the Consumer Contracts Regulations 2014 and you will not be permitted to receive a refund.
If you join online, the date of your membership application is the date you completed the online form. If you join by an offline method such as a phone call or paper membership form, the date of your application is the day the phone call or the paper form is received by the ALL office.
Beyond the 14 day period, you can cancel your ALL membership at any time. No refund will be given.
To cancel your ALL membership, you must submit a request to ALL in writing by post or by email to info@all-languages.org.uk.
1.2 Membership renewal
Your ALL membership works on the premise of continuous membership. A new subscription will automatically be created for you at your renewal date. You will be sent email reminders to make payment for your new subscription in advance of the renewal date.
ALL membership lasts for one calendar year from the date your membership application is received. If your membership application is received between the 1st to the 14th of the month (inclusive), your renewal date will be set to the 1st of that month, one calendar year later. If your membership application is received on the 15th or later of the month, your renewal date will be set to the 1st of the next month, one calendar year later. Your renewal date is displayed on your membership card and within the self service pages of the online ALL Members’ Area. You can also contact the ALL office using the information shown above for information on when your renewal is due.
1.3 Cancellation policy for renewing members
If you have received a renewal reminder and do not wish to continue your ALL membership, you must inform ALL in writing by post or by email to info@all-languages.org.uk no more than 45 days after your membership renewal date.
If your membership renewal fee remains unpaid after 45 days, your membership will be lapsed and you will no longer have access to the ALL membership benefits.
2. Data Protection
The terms of ALL’s data protection notification can be viewed on the Information Commissioner's website. (https://ico.org.uk/).
Any personal information you provide as part of your ALL membership application will be processed in accordance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998.
2.1 How will my information be used?
ALL collects, stores and processes your information in order to administer your ALL membership and deliver your membership benefits. The information is also used to support ALL marketing, sales, fundraising, events and research activities. Data will be retained by ALL if the membership is lapsed.
2.2 How do I make a choice about how my information is used?
You have a choice about whether you want to receive information about ALL and other organisations’ activities and opportunities, and by which channels. We will not use your personal information for these purposes if you have indicated that you do not wish us to do so. You can change your preferences at any time by contacting the ALL office:
Association for Language Learning
Voluntary Action LeicesterShire
9 Newarke Street
Leicester
LE1 5SN
Email: info@all-languages.org.uk
Association for Language Learning is a registered charity in England and Wales. Its registration number is 1001826.
Terms and Conditions - ALL Shop
1. Consumer Contracts Regulations (2014)
The Association for Language Learning is a registered charity in England and Wales (registered charity number 1001826). The main ALL office can be contacted at the following address: Association for Language Learning, Voluntary Action Leicestershire, 9 Newarke Street, Leicester, LE1 5SN. Telephone: 0116 478 8200. Email: info@all-languages.org.uk.
A postage and packaging charge will be added to all orders of physical products. This charge will be shown on the checkout page of the ALL website and also on your invoice.
If you opt to pay by invoice, payment in full is due within 30 days of the order being placed. Payment must be received and cleared before your order is posted out to you. ALL publications are not subject to VAT.
ALL accepts payment via online card payment, BACS, cheque, and card payment over the phone. If you do not make an online card payment at the time of placing your order, you will be sent an invoice via email detailing the payment methods available to you.
1.1 ALL member discount
ALL members receive a discount on the price of ALL publications. This means that the total cost of your order is subject to a satisfactory check being made on your ALL membership status. If you have claimed ALL member discount on the publications you have ordered, ALL will perform cross-checks against the ALL membership database to make sure that your ALL membership is active and fully paid. If your ALL membership is found to be inactive or unpaid, you will be contacted and asked to settle your ALL membership fee. If you do not wish to have ALL membership, you will be invoiced for the full price of the publications you have ordered.
Please note that if you claim ALL member discount on your order, and we find that your ALL membership fee is outstanding, we will place your order on hold until we have heard back from you.
1.2 Cancellation and returns policy – Physical goods
You have the right to cancel your order of physical goods and receive a full refund within 14 days of receiving your goods, provided that you return the goods in re-saleable condition. You are responsible for the cost of returning the goods.
To cancel your order, goods must be returned to the main ALL office and you must submit a request to ALL in writing by post or by email to info@all-languages.org.uk.
1.3 Cancellation and returns policy – Digital goods
If you access your digital goods before the expiry of the 14 day period, you are deemed to have waived your cancellation rights under the terms of the Consumer Contracts Regulations 2014 and you will not be permitted to receive a refund.
2. Data Protection
The terms of ALL’s data protection notification can be viewed on the Information Commissioner's website. (https://ico.org.uk/).
Any personal information you provide as part of your order will be processed in accordance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998.
2.1 How will my information be used?
ALL collects, stores and processes your information in order to administer and deliver your order. The data you provide will be cross-checked against the ALL membership database to determine your eligibility for any member discount. The information is also used to support ALL marketing, sales, fundraising, events and research activities. Data will be retained by ALL after the order is completed. Data will also be retained in the event that the order is cancelled.
2.2 How do I make a choice about how my information is used?
You have a choice about whether you want to receive information about ALL and other organisations’ activities and opportunities, and by which channels. We will not use your personal information for these purposes if you have indicated that you do not wish us to do so. You can change your preferences at any time by contacting the ALL office:
Association for Language Learning
Voluntary Action LeicesterShire
9 Newarke Street
Leicester
LE1 5SN
Email: info@all-languages.org.uk
Association for Language Learning is a registered charity in England and Wales, no.: 1001826.
Terms and Conditions - ALL Jobs Board service
1. Consumer Contracts Regulations (2014)
The Association for Language Learning is a registered charity in England and Wales (registered charity number 1001826). The ALL office can be contacted at the following address: Association for Language Learning, Voluntary Action Leicestershire, 9 Newarke Street,
Leicester, LE1 5SN. Telephone: 0116 478 8200. Email: info@all-languages.org.uk
Through purchasing a booking on the ALL Jobs Board service, your job vacancy will be promoted through ALL's channels as outlined in the ALL Jobs Board flyer. You can contact the ALL office using the details above if you need help with understanding the information provided on the ALL Jobs Board flyer.
The ALL Jobs Board service is not subject to VAT.
The total cost of your booking is shown on the checkout page of the online joining form, or, if you have placed a booking by contacting the ALL office directly, on your invoice. The amount must be paid in full within 30 days of the advert going live on the ALL Jobs Board. Instalments are not offered.
ALL accepts payment via online card payment, BACS, cheque, and card payment over the phone. If you do not make an online card payment at the time of placing the booking, you will be sent an invoice via email detailing the payment methods available to you. You can contact the ALL office using the details above to request more information on the balance outstanding and about the methods of payment available.
1.1 Cancellation policy for the ALL Jobs Board service
You have the right to cancel your ALL Jobs Board booking and receive a refund within 14 days of making your booking, provided your job vacancy did not go live. Going live refers to promotion of your vacancy through any of the ALL channels, which include but are not limited to:
- The ALL Jobs Board on the ALL website
- The ALL Twitter accounts
- The ALL Facebook account
- The ALL email newsletter, ALLNet
If you agree that your advert is to go live before the expiry of the 14 day period, you are deemed to have waived your cancellation rights under the terms of the Consumer Contracts Regulations 2014 and you will not be permitted to receive a refund.
Beyond the 14 day period, you can cancel your ALL Jobs Board booking at any time. No refund will be given.
To cancel your ALL Jobs Board booking, you must submit a request to ALL in writing by post or by email to info@all-languages.org.uk.
2. Data Protection
The terms of ALL’s data protection notification can be viewed on the Information Commissioner's website. (https://ico.org.uk/).
Any personal information you provide as part of your ALL Jobs Board booking will be processed in accordance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998.
2.1 How will my information be used?
ALL collects, stores and processes your information in order to administer your ALL Jobs Board booking and promote your booking. The information is also used to support ALL marketing, sales, fundraising, events and research activities. Data will be retained by ALL once the booking has ended.
2.2 How do I make a choice about how my information is used?
You have a choice about whether you want to receive information about ALL and other organisations’ activities and opportunities, and by which channels. We will not use your personal information for these purposes if you have indicated that you do not wish us to do so. You can change your preferences at any time by contacting the ALL office:
Association for Language Learning
Voluntary Action LeicesterShire
9 Newarke Street
Leicester
LE1 5SN
Email: info@all-languages.org.uk
Association for Language Learning is a registered charity in England and Wales. Its registration number is 1001826.
Login
Remember me
Forgot Password?
Sign In
Lost your password? Please enter your username or email address. You will receive a link to create a new password via email.
Pin It on Pinterest
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Ok
